Saeed Ghasemi

saeed.razii93@gmail.com 09375743511

06/2019

User Information

Birthday: 1996/18/02

Military Service Status: done // June 2019 to March 2021

Marital status: Single

Summary

Passionate laravel developer with 3+ years of experience building and maintaining websites as freelancer in the recruiting industry, Proficient in HTML, CSS, JS, PHP and modern libraries and frameworks such as JQuery, VueJs, Laravel, Bootstrap Designed REST APIs, worked on external systems integration, designed and implemented microservices. Recently I started to learning flutter just because of my interest.also I am familiar with GoLang.

- Friendly and patient
- Trustworthy
- Love to Learn
- · Passion for team-work
- Responsible

Education

Razi University

Software Engineering • Kermanshah, Kermanshah Province

Cooperation with MESFA laboratory

Skills

- PHP
- HTML5
- JavaScript
- Golang
- Gi
- · Solid Principles
- Redis

- Laravel
- · CSS3
- VueIS
- Flutter
- · Design Patterns
- · Rest API
- Bootstrap

Experience

MESFA

PHP Developer 10/2018 - 05/2019

FREELANCER

PHP Developer 04/2019 - Present

Projects

- apdideno.ir - otomata.ir - followbaz.ir

Languages

English

Persian